<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>zentechnista</title>
    <link>https://zentechnista.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on zentechnista</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 09:03:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zentechnista.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>151 Days Of Code</title>
      <link>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/08/151-days-of-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 09:03:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/08/151-days-of-code/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Like many, I started off 2017 with the #100DaysOfCode challenge. For the uninitiated, the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.100daysofcode.com/&#34;&gt;100DaysOfCode&lt;/a&gt; challengen involves coding a minimum of an hour each day, and tweeting your progress about what you&amp;rsquo;ve been working on and accomplished. While the focus of the challenge is to work on projects everyday, a mix of projecs and tutorials are still sufficient if you need some input before starting your next challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten Minutes Of Go</title>
      <link>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/07/ten-minutes-of-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 19:11:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/07/ten-minutes-of-go/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s probably no secret by now that I am a big fan of Go (also known as Golang), an open source programming language that is known for its speed and efficiency. As we move towards &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.golang.org/toward-go2&#34;&gt;Go 2&lt;/a&gt; and the eventual nuances and challenges that will come with its newest iteration, I want to take a few minutes to talk about what I think makes Go so special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prismastic Designs</title>
      <link>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/07/prismastic-designs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 23:31:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/07/prismastic-designs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most exciting (and difficult) parts of pursing any career is to step out of your comfort zone and start working towards your goals. There’s the mix of ‘am I going to be taken seriously‘, ‘am I truly ready for this‘, etc. But like all things, sometimes you just need to get your feet wet in order to make any progress and move forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons in Programming: Giving Yourself Credit</title>
      <link>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/07/lessons-in-programming-giving-yourself-credit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 06:52:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/07/lessons-in-programming-giving-yourself-credit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Author&amp;rsquo;s note: This post was originally titled &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rsquo;re awesome and should feel awesome&amp;rdquo;, but I realized that might be a bit of a mouthful.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For nearly all people who are learning to code on a non-traditional path (self study, bootcamps, etc.) it&amp;rsquo;s easy to experience feelings of doubt and discouragement. Not only can it be difficult going through the basics - picking a language, finding a good resource, and sticking to it without the structure of more traditional learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons in Programming: Learning To Get Uncomfortable</title>
      <link>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/07/lessons-in-programming-learning-to-get-uncomfortable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:49:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/07/lessons-in-programming-learning-to-get-uncomfortable/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Learning to get uncomfortable.&amp;rdquo; Kind of a weird article topic for a blog post right? There&amp;rsquo;s tons of articles on FOMO (Fear of Missing Out for the uninitiated), ignoring FOMO, sticking on the path of mastery, never giving up, knowing how to give up, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprints, Marathons, and Code</title>
      <link>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/07/sprints-marathons-and-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:48:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zentechnista.github.io/2017/07/sprints-marathons-and-code/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Roughly about 3 months ago to the day, I made an exciting decision to leave my previous job to join an e-commerce and social analytics startup. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t a particularly difficult decision - I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure wanting to hide under a rock ever Monday morning is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; a great sign that you&amp;rsquo;re enjoying your current position - but still, it represented a level of change that was both fun and intimidating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>